cimb.com 2013-12-17

# CIMB Group - General - Privacy

|   
---  
|   
---  
  
| 

Maintaining our clients' trust is critical to our success. We believe in the importance of safeguarding our clients' information while seeking to deliver premium financial solutions to our clients.  
  
---  
  
 **CIMB** :  
  
CIMB maintains strict security systems designed to prevent unauthorised access to your personal information by anyone, including our staff.   
  
**Data Security**  
  
Security is our top priority. CIMB will strive at all times to ensure that your personal data will be protected against unauthorised or accidental access, processing or erasure. We maintain this commitment to data security by implementing appropriate physical, electronic and managerial measures to safeguard and secure your personal data.

The secure area of our website supports the use of anti-virus detection, prevention and protection procedures and firewall barriers. Our systems are monitored to prevent unauthorised access. As a security measure, we will not send personal information to you by ordinary e-mail.  

 **Security Assurance**  
  
Both you and CIMB play an important role in protecting against online fraud. For purpose of user identity verification, we employ in our authentication process distinct Usernames and Passwords ("Access Codes") as key to access CIMB Research reports and other restricted information and pages.  

 **Collection of Personal Information**  
  
| | 

 **Use of "cookies"**  
  
---|---  
| 

Your visit to this Website may be recorded for analysis on the number of visitors to the site and general usage patterns. Some of this information will be gathered through the use of "cookies". Cookies are small bits of information that are automatically stored on a person's web browser in their computer that can be retrieved by this Website. Should you wish to disable these cookies you may do so by changing the setting on your browser. However, you will be unable to enter certain part(s) of this Website.  
  
|   
| 

 **Marketing Promotions**  
  
| 

Occasionally, we may collect personal information from visitors to this Website and those individuals that participate in a contest or promotion (online or over the telephone, or at one of our branches, or through any other means). Such information is only collected from individuals who voluntarily provide us with their personal information. We may use this information to advise them of products, services and other marketing materials, which we think, may be of interest to them. We may also invite visitors to this Website to participate in market research and surveys and other similar activities.

This Website may contain hyperlinks to other websites not operated by CIMB. CIMB is not responsible for the content, or the privacy practices, of these websites.   
  
|   
| 

**Disclaimer of Warranty and Limitation of Liability**  
  
| 

The information provided on this website is believed to be correct at the time of posting. CIMB or its affiliates do not make any representation or warranty, express or implied, as to the adequacy, accuracy, completeness or fairness of any such information and opinion contained on the website and accordingly, shall not be liable for any consequences of any reliance thereon. Neither CIMB nor its affiliates are acting as your advisor or agent. You should make your own independent assessment of the information herein, should not treat such content as advice relating to legal, accounting, and taxation or investment matters and should consult your own advisers.

It is not and should not be construed as an offer or recommendation to buy or sell securities. Neither does this website purport to contain all the information that a prospective investor may require. Because it is not possible for CIMB or its affiliates to have regard to the investment objectives, financial situation and particular needs of each person who reads the information contained herein, which may not be appropriate for all persons.

The information contained in this website may not be reproduced, redistributed, transmitted or passed on, directly or indirectly, to any other person or published, in whole or in part, for any purpose.  
  
|   
| 

 **The term "CIMB" denotes all Group companies within the CIMB Group and this Privacy Policy applies to the financial institutions there under.**
